iswish.com 2012-06-17

# Privacy Policy - iSwish

## Privacy Policy

The iSwish website is operated by iSwish Ltd (co number 2216785) and is referred to in this document as "we" "us" and "our". iSwish is committed to protecting and respecting the privacy of its users. In this policy we will outline our collection and usage practices. iSwish will maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of all personal information collected.

For additional information please review our [terms and conditions](http://www.iswish.com/terms-and-conditions).

## Collection of Personal Information

Personal information will be required from you when registering with iSwish or with any related service. Mandatory fields will be required when filling out your personal profile to include as a minimum; your name, email address, age, sex, country and city as well as non mandatory fields such as profile measurements; height, dress, shoe, bust, waist and leg size. Similarly, personal data may be collected for online promotions, competitions and surveys as well as signing up for email alert offers of items or features of interest.

We enable users to refer a friend to iSwish. This service or other email forwarding services, must not be used to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our privacy policy or terms and conditions.

It is our policy to ensure that your personal information will not be sold or for rent without obtaining your prior consent.

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient, and customised experience.

Information will be used to process transactions and used by website personnel and by persons or companies who perform operations or services relating to our business. Hence this information will be released to our business partners and Flow2cash. Flow2cash may also use this information to make credit checks and consult with fraud protection agencies.

Should iSwish decide to sell or buy any business or assets, we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. If iSwish Ltd or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

Account and other personal information will only be disclosed when one of the following is applicable:

  * Legal compliance and law enforcement including government agencies with statutory law enforcement responsibilities.
  * For court proceedings
  * Enforce or apply our terms and conditions
  * Protect the rights, property or safety of iswish Ltd, our users or others. 
  * Government agencies with statutory roles enabling them to request data from us including the Police and Inland Revenue.

Please [contact us](http://www.iswish.com/contact-us) should you wish to request whether this information has been provided.

Whilst we will look to ensure all personal information shared is held in a secure and proper manner, we cannot be held responsible for failure by any of our business partners to deal with your personal information in accordance with our legal obligations. Should you be directed to other sites that are beyond our control, we recommend you refer to these companies own policies in relation to the protection of your personal information.

If you wish to take dispute tribunal proceedings against another member, you can [contact us](http://www.iswish.com/contact-us) or the Disputes Tribunal for a statutory declaration, requesting contact details for the sole purpose of making a claim.

## Direct Marketing

It is the policy of iSwish to communicate with its members by mail, telephone, fax, email or other electronic messaging service regarding offers of goods and services or information that may be of interest to you. By provision of address, fax number, telephone numbers or email addresses you will be agreeing to be contacted by these methods for this purpose.

If you have agreed to our terms and conditions you will also receive newsletters, information on promotions and events we feel may be of interest to you. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies to improve and personalise our services. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us then simply indicate this when you register. In addition, newsletters will always indicate how members can remove themselves from the mailing list.

It is our policy to remove any member from any mailing list upon their request.

## Updating Your Personal Information

You may access your account details via your registered email and password which enables you to review and alter your personal information including changing your email address, password, phone number, etc. You are solely responsible for maintaining and updating your personal details and ensuring that this information is correct, current and complete and to have any inaccuracies in your information corrected promptly. iSwish will store previous email addresses against your profile to ensure compliance with our terms and conditions - in particular relating to the requirement of one account per member.

Should you wish to close your account, please [contact us](http://www.iswish.com/contact-us) and we will act as soon as reasonably possible.

## Account Protection

Your email address and password including fees are your responsibility and should not be disclosed to anyone. You are responsible for any activity on your account, including fees that are charged to your account. Should you choose to share your personal information with third parties who provide you additional services or other, you are responsible for all actions taken with this information and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy.

## Credit Card Security

We will endeavour to protect your credit card information during transactions by offering secure online transactions using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, which encrypts your information when transmitted over the internet. In addition, we are using Flow2Cash that provides a secure payment gateway (using API application programming interface) to connect to banking networks for authorisation of credit card transactions. iSwish retains only partial card details, however, they may be held by Flow2cash (review their privacy policy) .

When upgrading your membership or topping up your iSwish account by credit card, you may have the option to "save this card for next time". If you choose this option, your credit card details are encrypted and securely stored by Flow2cash.

It is recommended that you logout when you have finished online at iSwish to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer.

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files placed by us on your hard drive of your computer, when you visit certain parts of our site. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more customised service. In addition they enable us to:

  * Keep track of your current session and assist the functionality of the website 
  * Identify recurring visitors and to analyse your browsing habits 
  * Look at users' browsing actions and patterns, without identifying any particular individual
  * Estimate our audience size and usage pattern
  * Store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests
  * Speed up your searches

You may delete Cookies, however, in doing so you may be unable to access certain features on our site and could lose any information that enables you to access the site more quickly.

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies.

From time to time, iSwish may use Google's AdWords. This pay-per-click advertising programme appears on Google's search result pages and on the Google Network. Cookies are used to measure the number of Google users that click on an advertisement and visit certain iSwish pages, or who complete certain actions on the Website . Google provides this data to iSwish without identifying the users. [View Google's privacy policy](http://www.google.com/).

## Other Information Collected

For the purpose of improving and tailoring our service for its members, further information on interests, demographics or behaviours may be observed and collected by iSwish. This may include the URL that you came from (whether on our site of not) which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not) what browser you are using, and your IP address. Should users email or write to iSwish at any given time this information will be collected and stored in a personal file. Furthermore, users IP addresses will be keep securely at all times and only disclosed should law permit or in cases of fraud.

Any messages posted or feedback given for other members will be collected as will any personal correspondence by letter or email to us.

## Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy in the future as we deem necessary or as may be required by law. Such changes will be posted on the site and where appropriate we will notify you by email. You are deemed to have accepted the terms of the policy on your first use of the site following the changes.

## Contact

Should you require any further information, regarding this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us via the [contact us](http://www.iswish.com/contact-us) page.

### So what can you do now?
